A one man army.
Wrath of Man is a thriller, crime, drama film directed by Guy Ritchie.
A cold and mysterious new security guard for a Los Angeles cash truck company
surprises his co-workers when he unleashes precision skills during a heist.
The crew is left wondering who he is and where he came from.
Soon, the marksman's ultimate motive becomes clear as he takes
dramatic and irrevocable steps to settle a score.
H, played by Jason Statham.
Bullet, played by Holt McCallany.
Hollow Bob, played by Rocci Williams.
Boy Sweat Dave, played by Josh Hartnett.
Jackson, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Jan, played by Scott Eastwood.
Wrath of Man is a 2021 action thriller film directed by Guy Ritchie,
who co-wrote it with Ivan Atkinson and Marn Davies.
It is loosely based on the 2004 French film Cash Truck.
It is Ritchie's fourth directorial collaboration with lead actor
Jason Statham, and the first since Revolver (2005).
Holt McCallany, Jeffrey Donovan, Chris Reilly, Josh Hartnett, Laz Alonso, Raúl Castillo,
DeObia Oparei, Eddie Marsan, and Scott Eastwood appear in supporting roles.
In the film, H (Statham) is a new cash-truck driver in Los Angeles, whose thwarting of a
robbery leads to his skillset with guns and mysterious past being questioned.
Wrath of Man was released in several countries on April 22,
2021, and in the United States on May 7.
Despite receiving mixed reviews from critics, the
film grossed $104 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of robbery, affectation, crime boss, revenge, shootout.
The tone is emotional and intense.